What's wrong?
Am I disturbing you this late?
Happy birthday.
Did you set all this up?
Make a wish.
Mhm.
I hope this happy time
can last forever.
This is a gift.
Here.
Thank you.
Let me put it on for you.
Does it look good?
What are you doing?
Symmetry looks better.
Just you wait.
What's wrong, Mr. Wang?
Yufan, come to school right now.
So urgent?
Special circumstances. We'll talk when you get here.
Mr. Wang.
Why did you call me here in such a hurry?
It's the principal.
He wants to see you tomorrow morning.
I was really worried, so I contacted you first.
The principal wants to see me?
Yes.
Right now, at the school gate,
there's a group of people waiting for you, trying to collect debts.
You know about this, right?
Yes.
The principal is also worried.
He's afraid that
if they run into you
and make a big scene,
you might be in danger.
So,
he wants you to
take a leave of absence for a while.
So fast?
This is too sudden.
There's no other way.
The principal has to consider
the safety of all the students.
Then why did you ask to see me alone?
I think
you should insist on not taking a leave of absence.
At least,
hold on for another week.
Look,
do you remember this document?
Why are you here?
Are you cold?
How did it go?
The teacher was in such a hurry.
It must be something important.
Yeah.
I might have to leave school for a while.
Why is that?
Someone leaked my information.
Now people come to the school gate to block me every day.
It's all because of my dad's corporate debt.
But that's not your problem.
But the school needs to ensure the safety of every student.
I will be back soon.
I close my eyes,
listening to your heartbeat and breathing.
And at this moment, only we are left on Earth.
The shape of your smiling lips
always captivates my heart.
Principal.
Mr. Wang.
I brought him to you.
Come, take a seat.
Mr. Wang should have told you my thoughts.
He did.
He wants me to take a leave of absence.
The school
is considering the safety of you students.
We hope you can understand.
Principal, how about this?
Let Yufan
assist me first.
Once this campus loan sharking issue
is cleared up, he can take his leave of absence.
The investigation is the school's responsibility.
How can we let a student get involved?
I know, but right now,
this matter involves too many students.
Many are even connected to the student union.
We also need Yufan's help for this.
Can you give me three days?
I'll find the evidence within three days
and catch the mastermind.
Three days? Yufan, this is too risky.
Are you sure?
Are three days enough?
The school will fully support you.
For these three days, cooperate well with Mr. Wang's investigation.
Casting Associate Director: Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant: Li Kunxiao
Unit Vehicle: Yi Mingle
Yitong